mediaspider.us 2013-10-18

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

This document sets out how Lake Liberty uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

Lake Liberty makes every effort to ensure your privacy is protected. If we ask for certain information with which you can be identified when using this website, then be assured such information is only used according to this privacy policy.

Lake Liberty reserves the right to change this document as needed by updating this page without notice. You should check back with this page occasionally to remain up to date with any changes and to be certain you are satisfied with the policies and/or terms set out here.

**The Information We Collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * Name, job title and other personal information
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as zip code/postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * Information relating to your area(s) of business activity
  * Information relating to your website(s) and other related online activity
  * _**All users must be 18 years old or older**_

**The Use Of The Information We Collect**

We analyze the information to understand your requirements and provide better products, services and software, in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may send promotional communications about new or enhanced offerings, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting
  * We may also use your information to contact you for research purposes. We may contact you by various means
  * We may use the information for customizing the website to suit your interests

**Security Of Information**

We are fully committed to keeping your information secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure,we have suitable physical, electronic and operation procedures to guard and secure the information we collect.

**Use Of Cookies**

A cookie is a small, standard and common file placed on your computer's hard drive subject to your permission. Your permission may be manual and explicit or automatic depending on your device settings when you browse our website.

Declining cookies may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website and you may lose the use of some other functions.

Based on your agreement, the file is saved and the cookie holds small amounts of information relating to your preferences and choices when you visit a website.

Overall, cookies help provide a better website and service, by enabling us to see which pages are more useful to our users. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

Cookies enable websites and web applications to provide custom responses to you. The web applications can customize their actions and results to suit you.

**Linking To Other Websites**

Like most other websites, ours may link to other websites of interest. We do not have any control over the sites we link to. Additionally, while we may assess their content for suitability, subsequently we have no way of knowing when their content changes and whether any new or additional content or functionality is suitable or acceptable for you.

We cannot be held responsible for the safe keeping and privacy of any information you provide when visiting such external sites. This privacy policy does not govern any external sites. You must exercise extreme caution and thoroughly review the privacy statement governing any other site you visit before you share any information with them.

**Privacy Of Your Personal Information**

We will not sell, distribute or otherwise transfer your personal information to any third parties unless required by a court of competent jurisdiction to do so. The only exceptions are:

A)  When we use the services of third party entities such as our webhosting provider, email service provider and similar technical support organizations and then only on a need-to-know basis so we receive the required service.

B) The Limited Disclosure set out below

We may use your personal information to send you information about third party products and services which we think may be of interest to you.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please use the ‘contact us’ link on our website.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

You may contact us at:

MSSupport

[at]

mediaspider.us

**Limited Disclosure**

We may make use of a function that informs an existing service user when you take up our services via his website. The same function is equally provided to you so you are informed when anyone joins the service via your website.

The format of the information or the means of providing it may vary from time to time. However, the content is limited to only: your name, time/date of registration, the completion of your registration (Activated/Inactive) and your primary website.

We do not supply contact information and do not permit your referrer to publicise this information.
